[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "From what you've seen on the ground in Joplin, would you expect that death toll figure to rise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Sadly, Piers, I really want folks to have hope.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Joplin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "But there must have been moments last night when you were fearful for your life, wasn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oklahoma"]}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "What kind of a device given all of your experience would you give to the people of Joplin, given what may happen in the next few hours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Well, I think tonight, I mean, basically, looking at the weather pattern, I was out this afternoon chasing in northern Oklahoma, but there's a stationary front and there's what we call overlay, a lot of storms and hail and wind which will continue through the evening hours and then the bigger concern is going to be tomorrow.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Joplin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "In all your time, how bad would you say what you've been seeing is by comparison to other seasons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "This is definitely one of the more intense seasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Can you hear me, Tom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Yes, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Can you hear me, tom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Yes, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "How terrified were you during that process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "I was very scared.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Are you fearful, along with other people in Joplin, that you may get hit by another tornado?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "It's just made it very difficult to be able to locate people.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Joplin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", "RB", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Have you even thought about the rebuilding process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "To be honest with you at this point we're just focused on just being so thankful and I think there's a lot to be said for, if we could just as -- if we could just as easily forget our troubles, as easily as we forget our blessings, things would be far different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["spring"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Or from a meteorological point of view, is this kind of what happens every few years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Well, Piers, it's -- we always expect this clash of air masses in spring and as the warm air wants to overtake the cold air of winter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "And in terms of tornado seasons, to try and put this in correct perspective, is this as bad as you've seen tornado damage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "What does it feel like to be near a tornado of this devastation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "USINGER: It's always very cliche.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBN", ",", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "And Zach, how far away were your aunt and uncle from where you were?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "They were two to three miles from where I was, downtown, to the north.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zach"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Looking at the images that I'm looking at, which are just horrendous, given what you know of the town, would you say that there are likely to be more people that have died in this than the numbers that are being said at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "From things I heard from people who work at the hospital, I have to believe it's going to go a lot higher, which I hate saying that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "What kind of thing would you like to say to other people in Joplin, particularly as the weather is deteriorating again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Take cover.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Joplin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Are you sensing there may be another tornado tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Probably not tonight, Piers, but conditions we think tomorrow will be a different story.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Are we seeing really unusually bad weather or is it just these two incidents involving tornadoes that have come quite close together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Well, we're going to have to go back and go through data and really analyze things to find out exactly if there is a cause or if this is just a cycle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Have you -- in your darkest nightmares, you could never have imagined this kind of scene, could you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States", "Iceland"]}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "How bad do you think the situation is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Well, listening to the disaster on the tragedy you have just been describing in the United States, we are fortunate here in Iceland that nobody has been hurt, nobody has been killed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110523pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Are you anticipating a similar situation this time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "No, no, definitely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]